paragoncoin.com 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy

                                        Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you with understanding how www.paragoncoin.com
(“paragoncoin.com” "we", "us" or "our") collect, use and disclose the information you provide
us when accessing or using the website, www.paragoncoin.com.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion at any time. Any revisions to this
Privacy Policy will be posted on the homepage of our Website. It is your obligation to
periodically visit our Website to review any changes that may be made to this Privacy Policy.
Your continued use of our Website constitutes your agreement to be bound by any such
changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you are not
authorized to use our Website and your sole recourse is to not use our Website.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Website, you may provide us with two types of information: personal
information that you voluntarily disclose that is collected on an individual basis; and
information collected automatically when you use our Website or the services available on our
Website (collectively, the “Information”).
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is collected only when voluntarily offered and solely for purposes that
are clearly identified on our Website. Personal information means any information that is
unique to you, such as your:
Name
Username
Password
Email address
Cryptocurrency address
Mailing address
Other personal information you choose to provide
By providing us with your personal information, you also consent for us to collect, hold, use
and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition to
providing the foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with us through e-mail
or through the “contact” section of our Website, we may retain, use and disclose the content
of your messages together with your e-mail address and our responses.
What Information is Collected Automatically?
When you use our Website or services available on our Website, we automatically collect
information from your devices. We may collect the following information:

●         Server Log Information: We collect server log information when you use our Website,
which may include (but is not limited to) your login details, the date and time of visits, the
pages viewed, your IP address, time spent at our Website and the websites you visit just
before and just after our Website.
●         Device Information: We collect information about the computer or mobile device you
use to access our Website, including the hardware model, operating system and version, the
web browser you use, and other device identifiers.
●         Telemetry Information. If you use any of our open source software, we may collect
bandwidth upload and download speeds, the amount of free and used storage space on your
device and other statistics about your device.
●         Usage Information. If you use our Website, we will collect metadata about the files
you upload for storage and we will record instances in which you have used your private key
to authenticate communications.
●         Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We and our
service providers use various technologies to collect information when you interact with our
Website, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files that are stored on
your device when you visit a website, which enable us to collect information about your device
identifiers, IP address, web browsers used to access the Website, pages or features viewed,
time spent on pages, mobile app performance and links clicked. Web beacons are graphic
images that are placed on a website or in an email that is used to monitor the behaviour of
the user visiting the website or sending the email. They are often used in combination with
cookies.
Use of Information
We will only use the Information for purposes of:
●         providing, maintaining, delivering or improving our Website or the products or
services provided through our Website;
●         analyzing and tracking data to determine the usefulness or popularity of certain
content and to better understand the online activity of our Website users;
●         fulfilling our legal or regulatory requirements;
●         providing you with the information or products or services that you have requested;
●         answering your inquiry or responding to a communication from you;
●         developing new products or services;
●         sending you technical notices, support or administrative notifications;
●         communicating with you about news, products, services, events and other
information we think will be of interest to you;
●         matching your Information with job vacancies to assist us in finding a position that is
most suitable for you if you have contacted us about recruitment;
●         monitoring and analyzing trends, usage and activities in connection with our Website;
●         detecting, investigating and preventing fraudulent transactions or unauthorized or
illegal activities;
●         protecting the rights and property of the paragoncoin.com Parties (as defined below)
and others;

●         linking, connecting or combining Information we collect from or about you with other
Information; and
●         carrying out any other purpose or reason for which the Information was collected.
Sharing of Information
We will only share Information about you in the following ways:
●         with your consent or at your instruction;
●         with our current or future parent companies, affiliates, subsidiaries and with other
companies under common control or ownership with us or our offices internationally;
●         with third parties or service providers that perform work for us;
●         certain information you may choose to share may be displayed publicly, such as your
username and any content you post when you use interactive areas of our Website like our
online forums;
●         in connection with a merger or sale of our company assets, or if we do a financing or
are involved in an acquisition or any other situation where Information may be disclosed or
transferred as one of our business assets;
●         in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance
with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
●         if we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to
protect the rights, property and safety of any paragoncoin.com Party or others; and
●         with third parties where aggregate Information is disclosed which cannot be
reasonably be used to identify you.
Social Sharing Features
Our Website may offer social sharing features, links to social media and other integrated
tools. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your contacts or the
public, depending on the settings you use with the entity that provides the social sharing
feature or social media. Please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these
features to obtain more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and the
processing of such data by such entities.
Protection of Personal Information
We take reasonable steps to protect the security of the information communicated through
our Website. However, no computer security system is entirely foolproof and the Internet is
not a secure method of transmitting information. As a result, we do not assume any
responsibility for the data you submit to or receive from us through the Internet or for any
unauthorized access or use of that information and we cannot and do not guarantee that
information communicated by you to us or sent to you by us will be received or that it will not
be altered before or after its transmission to us. You agree to not hold us and our respective
past, present and future employees, officers, directors, contractors, consultants, equity
holders, suppliers, vendors, service providers, parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates,
agents, representatives, predecessors, successors and assigns (collectively, the
“paragoncoin.com Parties”) liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as a
result of any

misappropriation, interception, modification, deletion, destruction or use of information
provided through our Website.
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies as a default. You may wish to opt out by turning
off cookies (please refer to the help menu on your browser); however, switching off cookies
may restrict your use of our Website.
You may also opt out of receiving promotional communications from us at any time by
following the instructions in those communications. If you opt out, we may still send you non-
promotional communications, such as technical notices, support or administrative notifications
or information about your account (if you have one).
Hyperlinks and Third-Party Sites
This Website may contain links to other third party websites that may collect personal
information about you, including through cookies or other technologies. If you link to another
website, you will leave this Website and this Privacy Policy will not apply to your use of and
activity on those other websites. You should consult these other websites' privacy policies as
we have no control over them and are not responsible for any information that is submitted to
or collected by these third parties.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at
support@paragoncoin.com. Dated: August 15, 2017.
